<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tips and Tricks on Honduras Street Music</title>
    <link>https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tips and Tricks on Honduras Street Music</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Walkthrough - Getting Your Song Ready To Mix</title>
      <link>https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/getting-your-song-ready-to-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/getting-your-song-ready-to-mix/</guid>
      <description>Eliminate all guesswork from the mixing process through proper track preparation and by utilising strong communication and organisational skills.
Understanding Mixing Why hire a mixing engineer No access to a properly treated studio or the right gear New perspective - fresh, professional ears No time to learn, mix, and review! Where does it sit in the production process? Pre-Production Big picture decisions (instrumentation, performers, logistics) Songwriting Arrangement Tracking Recording vocals, instruments, drums, etc Editing Comp all tracks to use the best of each take Pitch and timing correction Mixing Balancing levels Panning Manipulating frequencies Shape dynamics Create space Add interest Ensure cohesion Export single stereo mix Mastering Final stage - finishing touches on a song, enhancing overall sound, gluing the sound of an album together Mix Engineer Expectations Early Communications Detailed conversation outlining your expectations Listen to their expectations and confirm Send a &amp;lsquo;premix&amp;rsquo; Send a reference track (or 3!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arranging Your Track For Orchestral Instruments</title>
      <link>https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/arranging-for-orchestral-instruments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/arranging-for-orchestral-instruments/</guid>
      <description>Bring the sound of the orchestra into your track can be intimidating. You can hear that soaring violin or the thrum of the cello but don&amp;rsquo;t know how to parley that into a coherent element of your song. Read on for some tips from professional players and arrangers!
Gallery / Unsplash In omni enim arte vel studio vel quavis scientia velas in ipsa virtute optimum quidque est. Quod est, ut dixi, habere ea, quae secundum naturam sint, vel omnia vel plurima et maxima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview - Finding The Right Drums For Your Song</title>
      <link>https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/finding-the-right-drums/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/finding-the-right-drums/</guid>
      <description>Drumming sits at the intersection of art and science. Your genre dictates certain sounds, but how do you get that magical &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo; factor that a truly inspirational rhythm part can bring? HSM sits down with drummer and producer XXXXXX to discuss how to approach this all important part of your track.
Gallery / Unsplash In omni enim arte vel studio vel quavis scientia velas in ipsa virtute optimum quidque est. Quod est, ut dixi, habere ea, quae secundum naturam sint, vel omnia vel plurima et maxima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding The Right Equipment For Your Sound</title>
      <link>https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/studio-equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://extraordinary-pasca-9bbb4b.netlify.app/posts/studio-equipment/</guid>
      <description>The sheer volume of kit available to an artist can be overwhelming and sorting through it take time from your music. Here are our suggestions for the best gear for each genre, artist type, and project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
