<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mastering on Honduras Street Music</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/mastering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mastering on Honduras Street Music</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/mastering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Walkthrough - Getting Your Song Ready To Mix</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/getting-your-song-ready-to-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/getting-your-song-ready-to-mix/</guid>
      <description>Eliminate all guesswork from the mixing process through proper track preparation and by utilising strong communication and organisational skills.
Understanding Mixing Why hire a mixing engineer No access to a properly treated studio or the right gear New perspective - fresh, professional ears No time to learn, mix, and review! Where does it sit in the production process? Pre-Production Big picture decisions (instrumentation, performers, logistics) Songwriting Arrangement Tracking Recording vocals, instruments, drums, etc Editing Comp all tracks to use the best of each take Pitch and timing correction Mixing Balancing levels Panning Manipulating frequencies Shape dynamics Create space Add interest Ensure cohesion Export single stereo mix Mastering Final stage - finishing touches on a song, enhancing overall sound, gluing the sound of an album together Mix Engineer Expectations Early Communications Detailed conversation outlining your expectations Listen to their expectations and confirm Send a &amp;lsquo;premix&amp;rsquo; Send a reference track (or 3!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding The Right Equipment For Your Sound</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/studio-equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/studio-equipment/</guid>
      <description>The sheer volume of kit available to an artist can be overwhelming and sorting through it take time from your music. Here are our suggestions for the best gear for each genre, artist type, and project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
